If you can't stand the heat, get out of Miami.
Bad Boys II is a action, crime, comedy film directed by Michael Bay.
Detectives Marcus Burnett and Mike Lowrey of the Miami Narcotics Task Force are
tasked with stopping the flow of the drug Ecstasy into Miami.
They track the drugs to the whacked-out Cuban drug lord Johnny Tapia, who is
also involved in a bloody war with Russian and Haitian mobsters.
If that isn't bad enough, there's tension between the two detectives when Marcus
discovers that playboy Mike is secretly romancing Marcus’ sister, Syd.
Detective Marcus Burnett, played by Martin Lawrence.
Detective Mike Lowrey, played by Will Smith.
Hector Juan Carlos 'Johnny' Tapia, played by Jordi Mollà.
Syd, played by Gabrielle Union.
Alexei, played by Peter Stormare.
Theresa, played by Theresa Randle.
Bad Boys II is a 2003 American action comedy film directed by Michael Bay, produced by Jerry Bruckheimer, and
the sequel to the 1995 film Bad Boys, in addition to the second film in the Bad Boys film series.
Martin Lawrence, Will Smith, Theresa Randle, and Joe Pantoliano reprise their roles from the previous film, and
they are joined by new cast members including Jordi Mollà, Gabrielle Union, and Peter Stormare.
The film follows detectives Marcus Burnett and Mike Lowrey
investigating the flow of illegal drugs going into Miami.
The film was released on July 18, 2003, by Sony Pictures
Releasing under the Columbia Pictures label.
It received generally negative reviews from critics; however, it performed well commercially,
grossing $273 million worldwide, becoming the tenth-highest-grossing film of 2003.
Two sequels, Bad Boys for Life and Bad Boys: Ride or Die,
were released in 2020 and 2024, respectively.
The film explores themes of drug smuggling, miami,
florida, undercover agent, cuba, ku klux klan.
The tone is lighthearted.